<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>heapcon ⬣ a new conference by heapspace</title>
    <link>https://heapcon.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on heapcon ⬣ a new conference by heapspace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://heapcon.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Splitt</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/martin-splitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/martin-splitt/</guid>
      <description>Martin is open source contributor and web evangelist by heart from Zurich with a decade experience from the trenches of software engineering in multiple fields.
He works as a software engineer at Archilogic in front- and backend. He devotes his time to moving the web forward, fixing problems, building applications and systems and breaking things for fun &amp;amp; profit.
Martin believes in the web platform and is working with bleeding edge technologies that will allow the web to prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arun Gupta</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/arun-gupta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/arun-gupta/</guid>
      <description>Arun Gupta is a Principal Technologist at Amazon Web Services. He is responsible for the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) strategy within AWS, and participates at CNCF Board and technical meetings actively. He particularly enjoys AMA on Containers and Serverless. He has built and led developer communities for 12+ years at Sun, Oracle, Red Hat and Couchbase. He has deep expertise in leading cross-functional teams to develop and execute strategy, planning and execution of content, marketing campaigns, and programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/about/</guid>
      <description> About us </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Code of Conduct Heapcon acknowledges that harassment has been a real, long-standing issue in the tech community. We also acknowledge that the technology sector is not wholly representative of the diverse makeup of our society.
Let us be clear We don’t approve harassment or offensive behavior, at our conferences or anywhere. It’s counter to our values. More importantly, it’s counter to our values as human beings.
Harassment includes offensive verbal comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion, technology choices, sexual images in public spaces, deliberate intimidation, stalking, following, harassing photography or recording, sustained disruption of talks or other events, inappropriate physical contact, and unwelcome sexual attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Soto</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/alex-soto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/alex-soto/</guid>
      <description>Alex is Java Champion and a software engineer at Red Hat in Developers group. He is a passionate about Java world, software automation and he believes in the open source software model. Alex is the creator of NoSQLUnit project, member of JSR374 (Java API for JSON Processing) Expert Group, the co-author of Testing Java Microservices book for Manning and contributor of several open source projects such as Arquillian ecosystem or Asciidoctor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ally Long</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/ally-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/ally-long/</guid>
      <description>Ally is a design lead at Field Intelligence. She’s worked on a broad array of projects – from public health software for NGOs and non-profits, to shiny brand experiences at agencies like Edenspiekermann and A Color Bright. She’d like to live in a place where sunscreen is a necessity, but makes do in Berlin. She travels as much as humanly possible, and spends a lot of her time working in West Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amahdy Abdelaziz</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/amahdy-abdelaziz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/amahdy-abdelaziz/</guid>
      <description>International technical speaker, Google developer expert (GDE), Oracle Developer Champion, trainer and developer advocate. Passionate about Web and Mobile apps development, including PWA, offline-first design, in-browser database, and cross platform tools. Also interested in Android internals such as building custom ROMs and customize AOSP for embedded devices. www.amahdy.net</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andraž Tori</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/andraz-tori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/andraz-tori/</guid>
      <description>Andraž is a technologist and an entrepreneur. In 2007 he co-founded Zemanta which was one of the first Slovenian start-ups. There he helped to develop an advanced programmatic advertising solution. Zemanta bids on billions of requests per day in order to buy native advertising space on behalf of brands. Zemanta was acquired by Outbrain in 2018. Before that, Andraž co-founded a slovenian cybercenter Kiberpipa and was a presenter on Slovenian National Television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Baxter</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/ashley-baxter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/ashley-baxter/</guid>
      <description>Ashley is building With Jack, business insurance on a first name basis. She likes video games, photography, and her dog, Indie. She is based in Glasgow, Scotland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courtney Hemphill</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/courtney-hemphill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/courtney-hemphill/</guid>
      <description>Courtney Hemphill is a Partner and Technical Lead at Carbon Five, a strategic digital product development firm. She has been developing software since 1999, first at an early stage e-commerce startup and eventually moving into consulting. She is currently managing the Carbon Five NYC team and helping retail, finance, and insurance companies in New York develop cloud-native, continuous delivery software for data management, APIs, and new product creation.
Courtney mentors for TechStars, is an advisor at several startups, and organizes coding workshops for women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Delabassee</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/david-delabassee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/david-delabassee/</guid>
      <description>David Delabassée (@delabassee) is a Software Evangelist working for Oracle; his primary focus is Java on the Server-Side including Java EE (Java Enterprise Edition). Prior to Oracle, David spent a decade at Sun Microsystems focusing on Java end-to-end, i.e. from the smart card to the high end servers. In his various roles, David has been involved in numerous Java projects since the early days of this technology.
David lives in Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepu K Sasidharan</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/deepu-k-sasidharan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/deepu-k-sasidharan/</guid>
      <description>Deepu K Sasidharan is the co-lead of JHipster. He has been part of the core JHipster team from its inception and is an active contributor to the project. He currently works for XebiaLabs, a DevOps software company, as a senior full-stack product developer. Prior to that, he worked at TCS as a technical consultant focusing on innovative solutions for Airlines. He has over 8 years of experience in architecture, design &amp;amp; implementation of enterprise web applications and pre-sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dejan Bosanac</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/dejan-bosanac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/dejan-bosanac/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eduards Sizovs</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/eduards-sizovs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/eduards-sizovs/</guid>
      <description>Eduards is a distinguished software architect and software development trainer who helps awesome teams around the globe excel at software architecture, engineering practices and soft skills. Eduards has trained hunders of senior developers, architects and engineering leaders Worldwide. Eduards leads Latvian Software Craftsmanship Community – the fastest-growing software development community in Latvia and organizes DevTernity – the top tech conference in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Jiang</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/emily-jiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/emily-jiang/</guid>
      <description>Emily Jiang is Liberty Architect for MicroProfile and CDI in IBM. Based at IBM&amp;rsquo;s Hursley laboratory in the UK, she has worked on the WebSphere Application Server since 2006 and is heavily involved in Java EE implementation in WebSphere Application Server releases. She is a key member of MicroProfile and CDI Expert Group, and leads the specification of MicroProfile Config and Fault Tolerance. Emily is also Config JSR co-spec lead. She regularly speaks at conferences, such as JAX, Voxxed, Devoxx US, Devoxx UK, Devoxx France, DevNexus and EclipseCon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felix Krause</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/felix-krause/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/felix-krause/</guid>
      <description>Felix is the creator of fastlane, an open source toolset for automating all your iOS and Android development tasks. He joined Twitter in 2015, and recently started working at Google, where he now works full-time on open source tooling for mobile app developers. Before that Felix worked at various startups in Europe and in the U.S. where he collected over 6 years of experience in the iOS ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Roberts</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/harry-roberts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/harry-roberts/</guid>
      <description>With a client list including Google, Unilever, and the United Nations, Harry is an award-winning Consultant Front-end Architect who helps organisations and teams across the globe to plan, build, and maintain product-scale UIs.
A Google Developer Expert, he writes on the subjects of CSS architecture, performance, and scalability at csswizardry.com, develops and maintains inuitcss, authored CSS Guidelines, and Tweets at @csswizardry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Thomas</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/james-thomas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/james-thomas/</guid>
      <description>James Thomas is a Lead Developer Advocate (Serverless) for IBM’s Cloud division. James is a huge fan of all thing serverless! He spends his time speaking at conferences, blogging or writing open-source code to share the awesomeness of serverless cloud platforms. James is a committer on Apache OpenWhisk, the open-source serverless platform. He wrote (and maintains) the official JavaScript client library. He also created the OpenWhisk provider plugin for The Serverless Framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jens Reimann</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/jens-reimann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/jens-reimann/</guid>
      <description>Loving Open Source, comitter at various Eclipse IoT projects, working for Red Hat, focusing on IoT since 1999, can make LEDs blink</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Seitz</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/jeremy-seitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/jeremy-seitz/</guid>
      <description>Jeremy Seitz is the CTO of Ricardo.ch, DIY hacker and modular synth enthusiast. Originally from America, he brings his experience and pragmatic approach on software engineering and IT management to Switzerland’s largest marketplace. During his 25-year career, he worked as a full-stack web and mobile developer, and later consultant and entrepreneur. He co-founded an interactive agency and a consulting firm that developed apps, games and projects for Nickelodeon, NBC, Timex, The New York Times, e-commerce, online gambling, museum exhibits, and various NY-based advertising agencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Carvajal</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/laura-carvajal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/laura-carvajal/</guid>
      <description>Laura has been a Software Engineer for 15 years and is currently a Principal Engineer at The Financial Times. She led the accessibility team for FT.com in 2016 and currently works in the Internal Products team at FT tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maciek Próchniak</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/maciek-prochniak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/maciek-prochniak/</guid>
      <description>Maciek Próchniak is algebraic topologist, for more than 12 years developing on JVM for food and pleasure. This includes various subjects varying from architecture to operations and from integration to web development. Recently mostly focused on integration and real-time stream processing. Likes to speak at conferences from Bergen to Cairo on wide range of topics – from Scala type system to streaming platforms. For 9 years happy @ TouK, and even more happy husband and father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Worthington</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/marianne-worthington/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/marianne-worthington/</guid>
      <description>Described as brilliant, hilarious, awesomesauce and so engaging you’ll forget to eat your snacks, Marianne has trained over 10,000 people in nearly every state. Recently she was recognized as one of the top trainers in America. She is the founder of Work Warrior, a company that helps managers become rockstars. In 2018 she decided to launch her second brand, Sequins and Superheroes, where she helps people manage themselves, and become the hero of their own story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Heckler</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/mark-heckler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/mark-heckler/</guid>
      <description>Mark Heckler is a Pivotal Principal Technologist &amp;amp; Spring Developer Advocate, conference speaker, published author, &amp;amp; Java Champion focusing upon developing innovative production-ready software at velocity for the Cloud and IoT applications. He has worked with key players in the manufacturing, retail, medical, scientific, telecom, and financial industries and various public sector organizations to develop and deliver critical capabilities on time and on budget. Mark is an open source contributor and author/curator of a developer-focused blog (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximiliano Firtman</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/maximiliano-firtman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/maximiliano-firtman/</guid>
      <description>Max Firtman is a mobile and web developer with over 20 years of experience. Spent 15 years teaching Web development to beginners and advanced developers in more than 40 countries - including big companies such as Apple, Yahoo!, PayPal and Intel. He has authored more than 10 books available in 13 languages, most recently High Performance Mobile Web published by O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media.
He has received different recognitions, including Nokia Developer Champion yearly since 2006; Adobe Community Champion in 2011, and a Google recognition for being one of the most innovative mobile developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Ducy</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/michael-ducy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/michael-ducy/</guid>
      <description>Born on the rolling plains of central Illinois corn fields, Michael Ducy started his technology journey at a young age. Always curious, he was once threatened that he’d never have toys bought for him again if he didn’t stop taking them apart to see how they worked. Raised in a blue collar family, his first workbench was given to him at the age of 5. His first programming language was BASIC, at the ripe young age of 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milen Dyankov</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/milen-dyankov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/milen-dyankov/</guid>
      <description>Milen is a Developer Advocate at Liferay and focuses on Java and OSGi Platform. He is passionate about designing and building software as well as helping others design and build good software! After more than 15 years developing, designing and consulting on various Java EE solutions for leading European companies, he currently spends most of his time teaching, speaking at conferences all over the world and researching his favorite topics around Java modularity, μservices, distributed systems architecture and software craftsmanship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narendra Shetty</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/narendra-shetty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/narendra-shetty/</guid>
      <description>Narendra is a Frontend Developer at Booking.com. He is been working with React &amp;amp; React Native for over a year now. He cares about performance and believes that performance is a key for conversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Stevenson</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/neil-stevenson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/neil-stevenson/</guid>
      <description>Neil is a solution architect for Hazelcast, the leading operational data management company. In more than 25 years of work in IT, Neil has designed, developed and debugged a number of software systems for companies large and small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Kettner</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/patrick-kettner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/patrick-kettner/</guid>
      <description>Patrick Kettner won an eighth grade talent show competition singing Gloria Gaynor’s 1978 disco hit “I Will Survive”, and things have been looking up ever since. He has traded in the golden microphone for a PM position on Microsoft Edge, as well as being the lead developer for Modernizr. He lives in Seattle with his wonderful partner Katrina, son Holden, and dog Baxter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paula R. Stern</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/paula-r-stern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/paula-r-stern/</guid>
      <description>Paula Stern is the founder and CEO of WritePoint Ltd. She is a senior technical writer, long-time Adobe Technical Communications Suite user, and has presented at numerous conferences in the UK, Ireland, Germany, India, Israel and the US. She is the main instructor and designer of the WritePoint Technical Writing Course, a former Adobe Influencer, and the current founder and President of tekom-Israel. Paula lives in Israel, is married and has five children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter O&#39;Shaughnessy</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/peter-oshaughnessy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/peter-oshaughnessy/</guid>
      <description>Peter is a developer advocate in Samsung&amp;rsquo;s mobile web browser (Samsung Internet) team. He enjoys helping web developers to make the most of the web platform, especially up-and-coming Web APIs. In recent months he has been exploring and sharing about PWAs, Web Payments, WebXR and Web Bluetooth. He has been a developer since 2003, previously working at a “future technologies” lab at an education company and as a tech lead at a national newspaper and two web development agencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radoslav Stankov</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/radoslav-stankov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/radoslav-stankov/</guid>
      <description>Radoslav is a web developer for more than a decade. He believes that frontend and backend are equally important. In the last several years he juggles between Ruby and JavaScript projects. Organizer of . Currently works at Product Hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rustam Mehmandarov</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/rustam-mehmandarov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/rustam-mehmandarov/</guid>
      <description>Passionate computer scientist. Leader of the biggest community-driven Java conference – JavaZone; Norwegian JUG - javaBin. Community builder. Consultant. Developer. Speaker. Java Champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stacy Stubellfield</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/stacy-stubellfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/stacy-stubellfield/</guid>
      <description>Stacy Stubblefield co-founded TeleSign in 2005 and today helps to drive TeleSign&amp;rsquo;s product strategy and identify opportunities for innovation&amp;ndash;ensuring that TeleSign delivers groundbreaking technology that best addresses market needs. As part of TeleSign&amp;rsquo;s founding team, she was instrumental in conceptualizing and developed its platform and patented technology. While developing TeleSign&amp;rsquo;s technology, she also oversaw an engineering team at an internet incubator that launched several fast-growing web properties. She remains an active consultant, advising internet start-ups and consumer product sites and is a frequent speaker at industry events, including Mobile World Congress and Mobile Computing Summit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Tynjä</title>
      <link>https://heapcon.io/speakers/tommy-tynja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heapcon.io/speakers/tommy-tynja/</guid>
      <description>Senior software engineer and continuous delivery consultant at Diabol. An advocate of open source software, continuous delivery, test-driven development, automation and tools that boost developer productivity and get software shipped faster. Specializing in systems running on the Java platform. Has been contributing to various open source projects over the years, such as Arquillian and Apache TomEE. Currently maintainer of the Jenkins Delivery Pipeline plugin. Co-founder of the Continuous Delivery Stockholm meetup group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>